Guide to the Calhoun College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2016 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Calhoun College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1964-2016 maintained by the dean
1960-2016
RU 255
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
122
(172 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Calhoun College, Yale University.
Calhoun College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-E-1 (YRG 13-E-1), Records of the dean of Calhoun College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Calhoun College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Calhoun College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-363
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
- Student records for the Classes of 1974-1978 (impounded), Accession 1975-A-003; 4.75; (6 boxes)
  Access is restricted.
- Student records for the Classes of 2003 to 2016, Accession 2018-A-0078
  Student records are restricted until 2092 as established by Yale Corporation regulations http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives.
  - Class of 2003
    - Ahn, Alison Myong-Jin, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Angelson, Meredith Jane, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Arian, Elena Hope, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Augusztiny, Hali Eliza, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Babst, Cynthia Morgan, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Baker, Griffin Leonard, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Baron, Danielle Rachel, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bennett, Jennifer Dale, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Blumer, Mackenzie Hughes, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bradley, Timothy Evans, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Letesha Tuwana, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Chang, Karl, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Chen, Michelle Zhong Mei, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cotto, Anthony Gracia, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Crawford, Robert C.L., 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Danes, Claire Catherine, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      General
      Did not graduate.
    - Degani, Nicholas Anthony, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Den, Elena Ida, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dinner, Mark, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Elder, Benjamin Daniel, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Farley, Najah Aaquila, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Feng, Cindy Hsin-I, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Fenster, Amman David, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fields, Shawn Eric, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Fiftal, Ryan David, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Fireman, Jonathan France, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Freeman, Bryan Rudolph, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - French, Kathryn Lee, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Friesenhahn, Michael Edward, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Gabrielson, J. Scott, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Garcia, Jonathan, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Geier, Andrew B., 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Glass, Noah Nelson, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Gonzales, Mia Noel, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Gray, Jill, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Greenleaf, Maron Estelle, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Gutman, Eve Rachel, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Hammond, Laura Elizabeth, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hart, Julia Roberta, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Hermann, Elizabeth Rachel, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Hinojosa, Stephanie Renee, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Honig, Rebecca, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Horak, Laura Evelyn, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Indyk, Sarah Emily, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Isler, Ozan, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Jenks, Amanda Joy, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Jitkoff, Tatiana Adrian, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Jones, Stephanie Nicole, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Kass, Alexander Michael, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Kinsolving, Arthur Bernard, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Klay, Benjamin William, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Knapp, Esther Elise, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Kops, Peter, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Kornberg, Michael Davin, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Kriegman, Joshua, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Kroplick, Deborah Connie, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Landy, Benjamin David, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Laves, Ellen, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Le, Hoang-Tuoc Pham, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Montgomery, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lemly, Diana Catherine, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - LePatner, Evan Harris, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lin, Victoria Hisayo, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lobert, Joshua Thomas, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mabuchi, Shohei, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Magram, David Nathan, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Mangini, Lauren Dominica, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Manning, Sara Michelle, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mathis, Walter Stanley, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Maynard, Kelly Reid, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - McEwan, Caitlyn Boynton, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - McGoey, Michelle Theberge, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - McGuire, Joseph Thomas, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Mechoulam, Patricia Flora, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Milewski, Jared Richard, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Milsom, Alexandra Lauren, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Mitchell, Lindsay Werner, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Mittman, Wesley Meredith, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Morris, Benjamin, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Najarian, Mesrop Armen, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Ni, Thomas Kang-His, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - O'Neill, Regan Patrick Tatsuo, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Palmer, Brian Russell, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Pareles, Marissa, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Park, Chi Wan, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Parkhurst, William Marshall, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Porter, Eldon Grant, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Powanda, Allysha Ida, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Powers, Jeremy Cushing, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Rubenstein, Beth Lisbin, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Shaw, Edward Peter, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Schneider, Eric Jay, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Schulze-Halberg, Nils, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Shen, Jessica, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Singer, Sarah Elizabeth, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Skinner, Harlyn Gynette, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Slosar, Magdalena, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Smalls, Natasha Cherie-Monquie, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Spencer, Andrea E., 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Spencer, Joanna Louise, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Squadron, Daniel Louis, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sullivan, Thomas David, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Suranimala, Monalee Sadhana, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Tejerina, Diana Sarah, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Thompson, Scott Anderson, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Tookes, Hansel Emory, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Tracy, Lindsay Robin, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Turner, Caleb McCracken, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Watson, Rachel L., 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Webber, Mitchell Doron, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Wolrich, Charles Christopher, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Wright, Carolyn Marie, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Wu, Mary, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Yuspeh, Andrew, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Zaremby, Justin Scott, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Class of 2004
    - Ahmad, Assad, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Aleman, Diana, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Areson, Christopher, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Arnaudo, Juliet, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Augustine, Paul, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Baker, Elizabeth, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Barta, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Beard, Robert A., 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bewley, Marie, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Block, Katherine, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Braun, Maureen, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Brown, Ellen, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bruce, Robert Colson, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Carey, Colleen, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Carrier, Shannon, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Chang, Christine, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Cheng, Gino, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Christoforou, Steven, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Chung, Sunchoo, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Cohen, Jessica Lee, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Corbin, Zachary, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Cruikshank, Benjamin Bryan, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      Withdrawn
    - Dabela, Amsalu, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Davidson, Andrew, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Dearborn, Meredith Richardson, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - DeMarchis, Livia, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - De Santiago, Ana, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Dreier, Lucas, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Dwyer, Jeffrey Stephen, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Ellis, Stephanie, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Espinoza, Michael Lee, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Esteves, Charles, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Feigenbaum, Aaron, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Filson, Shayna, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Fleisher, Madeline, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Gold, Michael, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Goode, Aaron, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Grundy, Christopher, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Halfon, Johanna, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hauser, Yael, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Henry, Elliot, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hayes, Tameka Joy, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hoppin, Erin Sommer, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Hudak, Christopher, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Hung, KaYen, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Jarnebrant, Peter, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Jean, Dorothy, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Jester, Lindsay, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Joseph, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Kang, Jane, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Klema, Michael, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Kopec, Aleksandra, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Krueger, Michael, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Kwok, Edward Ho-Lai, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lakhani, Hafeez, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - LeDonne, Gregory, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Lee, Mark, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Lerner, Nicole, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Levi, Benjamin, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Lew, Victoria, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Lin, Diana, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Lucas, Joshua, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Maiers, Tanya, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Matthews, Andria Danielle, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Milch, Adam, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Miller, Trista, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Minier, Jerry, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Minter, Namik, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mitropoulou, Christina, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Moghadam, Mahbod, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Mostyn, Santiago, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Mpi, Oroma, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Muchmore, Evan, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Murphy, Prescott, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Najbauer, Noemi, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Natrajan, Rekha, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Nesburg, Kristine Anne, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Page, Danielle, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Pattillo, David, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pemberton, Crystal, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Petrin, Christopher, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pham, Christine, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Pollack-Pelzner, Emma, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Powers, Albert, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Pugh, Meghan, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Purcell, Margaret, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ramirez, Alma, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Reid, William, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Rona, Luke, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Rosic, Nicholas, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Schnoebelen, Katrina, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Shea, Sebastian, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Sheard, Emiko, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sheridan, Jennifer Friedrich, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Shin, Daniel Hyun, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Simon, Justin, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - So, Perry, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Storm, Oliver, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Strom- Weber, Angela, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sutha, Ken, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Tirado, Jesus, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Tolaney, Neil, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Tyebjee, Zia, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Voorhees, Jennifer, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Walton, Monique, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Waterford, Herman, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Witkowski, Alicja, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Worthington, Brooke, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Wright, Richard, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Class of 2005
    - Ambler, Charles, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Atkins, Michael, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Azure, Anastasia X., 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Benoit, Marisa, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Best, Rebecca, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Bewley, Benoit, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Bloniarz, Adam, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Bloom, Matthew, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Bostic, John, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Brady, Christopher, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Braff, William, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Brenner, Adam, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Brogan, Jacob, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Brooks, Meredith, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Burkhard, George, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Chiang, Hyo Jin, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Chiu, Simon, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Click, Adam, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Clinton, Miriam, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Crawford, Charles, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Cruz, William, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Cumberbatch, Gavin, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - De Santis, Lisena, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Duggan, Erin, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Epstein, Liana, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Estrada, Lenore, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Finegan, Annelise, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Friedlander, David, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Gaviria, Carlos, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Glassco, Sylvia, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Goldberg, Miriam, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Gopisetty, Smita, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Greenwold, Diana Jocelyn, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Grobe, Christopher, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Hamso, Magni, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Henderson, Kirk, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hong, Dennis, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Hutt, Ethan, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Jones, Kevin, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Shawndra, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Kahn, Daniel, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Kamody, Lenore A., 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Keidel, Carly, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Kelly, Bridget, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Kienzle, Justin, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Kim, Sallie, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Krinsky, Benjamin, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Kroehle, Scott, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Kwak, Jiyoung, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - La, Phuoc, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Layer, Noelle, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Levin, Paul, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Lewis, Alexandra, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Lieu, Nita, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Lindquist, Robert, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Lo, Katherine, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Lopez, Catherine, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Maier, Jackson, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Manix, Marc, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Meyers, Faith, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Miller, Bryan, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Nadler, Seth, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Ngo, Lee, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Nogasky, Megan, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Nou, Eric, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Paindiris, Jessica, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Patel, Anoop, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Perry, Avi, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Pettigrew, Erin, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Piro, Jennifer, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Rausch, Karly, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Reagan, Matthew, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Rivlin, Kathleen, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Rojas, Jordan, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ryan, John, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Santovasi, Daniel, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Schroll, Lindsay, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Shackleton, Jeffrey, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Shankar, Meera, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Shum, Keane, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Siger, Steven, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Sims, Katherine, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Katherine, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Stevens, Leo, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Strauch, Thomas, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Sullivan, Andrew, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Sun, Lihan, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Tang, Aaron, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Thompson, Heather, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Thompson, Lauren, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Toscano, Laura, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Towber, Michael, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Triggs, Elizabeth, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Tritipeskul, Patcharin, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Truong, Anh, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Vazquez, Caroline, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Wagner Partin, Sally, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Wang, Lucy, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Weisfield, Shellie, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Willis, Nicole, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Zamora, Melodie, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Burnat, Kyle Matthew, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Deceased.
  - Class of 2006
    - Barrick, Adam Matthew, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Benaim, Alexander Gabriel, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Boquin, Alberto Jose, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Borden, William Sutton, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Bowman, Ashley Dionne, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Bradley, Zachery Adam, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Brady, Paula Christine, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Carpman, David Paul, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Catambay, Danielle, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Cerin, Milliejane Lindgrensavage, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Chen, Michael Cunyuan, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Chen, Sarah, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Cloobeck, Melinda, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Coburn, Tyler, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Cooper, Kelly Nicole, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Craig, Matthew Stuart, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Curran, Kaitlin Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Dabela, Ellen Abraham, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Taylor Lloyd, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - DelVecchio, Alexis Lopez, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Elder, Katherine Rachel, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Farber, Molissa Heather, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Fealey, Matthew Francis, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Feinstein, Jessica Kate, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Feng, Lynn Shi, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Friend, Nicholas Gradeck, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fuentes, Jose Rodrigo, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Fuldner, Carl Christian, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gagne, Claire Maile, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Gartner, Joshua Michael, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Gleason, Paul Wermager, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Grant, Nicole Antoinette, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hagemann, Christopher Gray, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hansberry, Heidi Lee, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Herbert, John Benjamin, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Herschkopf, Marta Debra, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hongladaromp, Pras, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Huttner, Nathan Irving, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Hwang, Seockhwan, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Jackson, James, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Jacob, Alex Benjamin, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Janco, John M., 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kant, Lisa Ann, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Kasinath, Vivek, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Kendrick, Samuel Ross, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Kim, Sunny, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Klingenstein, Daniel, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Koffler, Daniel Matthew, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Korobkin, Rachel Tess, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Kupperman, Ashley Isaac, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Lambert, Aaron Lee, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Lombardi, Patrick Michael, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Maciunas, Jonas Vincas, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Manville, Laura Maria Egan, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Matthews, Mary Elizabeth, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Meyer, Christina Tsacoumis, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Milch, Elizabeth Weil, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Millman, Alexander James, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Monaghan, Tess Lindsey, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Moore, Susanna Thornton, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Moros, Sarah, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Nelson, Kate E., 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - O'Reilly, Taryn Jane, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Page, Amelia Boorse, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Paidipaty, Sailaia Mangala, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Paluf, Christen Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Pavlicek, Beth Marie, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Peace, Brett, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Preciado, Mariana Alejandra, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Rahman, Marina, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Rebeiro, Peter Francis, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Reider, Abigail Libby, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Rodarte, Cesar Rodrigo, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Romney, Arianne Allaire, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Rubin, Tamar Aliza, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Scharf, Jennifer Ellen withdrawn, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Schneider, Todd William, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Schram, Andrew William, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Schwab, Michael Lawrence, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Selig, Sarah Jane, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Shi, Andrew, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Shiflett, Nicole Jane, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Silver, Sabrina Naomi, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Simone, Rudolph Francis, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Soegaard, Jose Antonio, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 20)